

**TRAN DANG TIEN** 

**IT INTERN** 



With the programming knowledge I have gained from my university years, I hope I can apply it into practice in an internship position. With this opportunity, I hope I can obtain my knowledge and experience to become a Fullstack Developer in the future.

# Work experience

06/2023 - 07/2023

Tutor

**ICANTEHC** 

Support Html/Css/Python code combat and practice instructions for students.

# **Activities**

08/2023 - Now

Html/Css/Php/Mysql

Selling coffee website

Website interface, login, register, curd,...

06/2023 - Now

Html/Css/Js

Portfolio website

Mobile, desktop website interface, click event,...

11/2022 - 01/2023

Html/Css

Portfolio website

Mobile, desktop website interface, click event,...



**Phone** 

**Email** 

**Address** 

0842804068



dangtien.tdt@gmail.com



Tran Van Du, Ward 13, Tan Binh District, HCM



Website

https://dtien15.github.io/web\_portfolio/



15/01/2002





Male



# **Education**

Ho Chi Minh University of Natural Resources and **Environment** 

| 2020 - 2024

## **INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

Academic pretty



# **Skills**

## HTML5 & CSS3

Responsive

Figma to html\css

## **JAVASCRIPT**

Dom/Event

## PHP/MYSOL

MVC

#### **WORDPRESS**

Basic

## **GITHUB**

Basic



# **Certifications**

F8

Khóa học HTML CSS Pro F8